《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...
你可能觉得发生的这一切都是你的错
You're probably thinking what happened was your fault.
我是来告诉你这不是你的错
I'm here to tell you that it's not.
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
这只是一个人的错
It's the fault of only one man,
而我们将去阻止他
and we're going to stop him.
还记得我答应过你什么吗
Do you remember what I promised you?
翻译   PiPi  Murrayzhang  补课狂魔
一个新的开始
A new beginning.
你会拥有的
And you will have it.
我见识过他用他的能力能做些什么
I've seen what he can do with his powers,
翻译    Silence  ET外星人  桃子西
但当他试图把那种能力用在我身上时
but when he tried to use them on me,
竟然伤害到了他自己
it completely backfired.
校对   苹果果 Z小花儿 沫沫
精校   陈小圈
而且我嗜血的欲望也消失了
And my bloodlust was gone.
帮我想个办法永久摆脱这种欲望
Help me figure out a way to make that permanent.
时间轴风吹来的那片云
总有一天  我会有机会
One day I will have my moment,
杀了你
and I will kill you.
把她拿下
Take her.
特效&后期   咖啡Lee[绿箭侠]       总监   苹果果
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
不用费心了  她不会吃的
拉斯·厄尔·高福命令保证囚徒的健康
把这些都拿走
Take that away as well.
食物会招来蚊虫
The food attracts flies.
我想自己清静
And I prefer my solitude.
辣椒是园子里的
The pepper came from the garden.
你不在园子依旧茂盛
The garden grows strong even in your absence.
还是吃点吧
Please try a bite.
去  通知其他守卫
她跑了
快  我们得...
到明天早上这座山就是我们的了
The mountain will be ours by morning.
我们得快点行动
We must act quickly.
那个篡位者会带着追随他的人回来
The usurper will return, and with him, his followers.
圣莲找到了吗
Has the Lotus been found?
在九州  有人严加看守
In Kyushu. It's well guarded.
这里曾经也被严加看守
So was this place upon a time.
好消息  那个毛贼朝着你去了
Good news, the burglar is headed straight towards you.
坏消息  那个毛贼正朝着你去了
Bad news, the burglar is headed straight towards you.
不许动
Freeze!
他从哪学的这本事
Where did he learn to do that?
我猜是太阳马戏团
I'm thinking Cirque du Soleil.
他朝屋顶去了
He's headed for the roof.
多谢了  黑金丝雀
Thank you, Black Canary.
该你们出场了  绿箭侠和快手
That is your cue, Green Arrow and Speedy.
-她这是  -滥用我们的代号吗
- Is she-- -Overusing our code names?
没错  由她去吧
Yep. Indulge her.
我们找到他了  守望者
We got him, Overwatch.
你不知道我有多喜欢听你喊我的代号
You have no idea how much I love hearing that.
其实我们知道
I think we do, actually.
天台有两扇门
Two rooftop doors.
平面图显示楼梯把你们下面分成了一个错层
Floor plans show that the staircase splits a level below you.
艾美科技
他可能从任何一个门出来
He could come out either door.
抓到他了
Got him.
快手
Speedy!
绿 箭
第四季  第十二集
西娅怎么样了
How's Thea?
她没事  在我们家休息
She's OK. She's resting at our place.
她说只是有点累
She said it was just exhaustion.
我们都不相信这话  对吧
We don't believe a word of that, do we?
不然会是怎样
What else could it be?
复活泉水
The pit.
嗜血会让她凶猛
The bloodlust makes her feral,
不会让她昏迷
it doesn't make her lose consciousness.
而且西娅已经很久没有暴力过了
And Thea hasn't gone aggro in months.
没错  说不定这正是
Exactly. Maybe this is some sort of side effect
她这么艰难挺过来的副作用
of her white-knuckling her way through it.
这种推论有点牵强
It seems like a bit of a leap.
奥利  你在想什么呢
Ollie, what are you thinking?
我应该更细心
That I should have done a better job
照顾好她
of keeping an eye on her.
她告诉我她的嗜血两个月前又出现了
She told me the bloodlust came back two months ago
我却全然不知
and I didn't even know.
我心思一直在竞选上
I've been focused on the campaign
而且我还一直往返中城
and I've been running back and forth to central city and...
你怎么总是所有事情都怪自己
How is it that you always manage to blame yourself for everything?
那是他的超能力  愧箭侠
That's his super power. Guilt Arrow.
刚才那个毛贼从艾美科技偷东西了吗
Did our thief steal anything else from Amertek?
一个网络映射器
A network mapper.
它可以扫描
A piece of tech designed to scan
附近所有的电子设施
all nearby digital infrastructure
找出其潜在的弱点
for potential vulnerabilities.
这会是他最后一票吗
Do we think it's his last score?
希望如此
We better hope that it is.
艾美科技是星城
Amertek's one of the last
所剩无几的企业之一了
viable businesses left in Star City.
看来帕尔默科技也是其中之一
Turns out Palmer Tech is one of those viable businesses.
至少目前是
For now, at least.
目前是什么意思
What do you mean for now?
董事会真是智慧无穷
The board, in their infinite wisdom,
他们决定把柯蒂斯那个改变世界的新科技
decided to move the presentation
展示时间从四月提前到现在
on Curtis' world-changing tech from April to now.
猜猜谁现在要去面对那个潜在大灾难
And guess who gets to be the face of that potential disaster?
那你想让我陪你去吗
Oh, well, do you want me to come with you
给你点精神支持
for a little moral support?
不用了  我没事
Ahh, no, I'll be fine.
这次只是排练
It's just a dry run.
帕尔默科技
在过去三十年里
In the past 30 years,
电池技术实际上一直没有进展
battery technology has been at a virtual standstill
电池寿命和19世纪70年代相比
with batteries lasting no longer than they did
并没有变长
in the 1970s.
可恶
Damn it.
但是
Uh, but
帕尔默科技研制出了超能电池
with Palmer Tech's power cell,
这是一个重大突破
it represents a major breakthrough.
抱歉
Sorry.
该用投影仪的
Should have gone with overhead projector.
霍特先生
Mr. Holt.
能否让我们两个单独谈谈
Could you give us the room, please?
这好像有点困难
Well, actually, that's gonna be a little difficult,
因为这整栋楼资产都是...
seeing how the entire building's the property of--
我...我这就出去
i'll just-- I'll be right outside.
费莉西蒂
Felicity.
我能有话直说吗
May I be uncomfortably honest?
你不一直都这样吗
Well, you have never shown an inability to do so before.
也对
Right.
公司在你返回星城之前
This company has been flirting with bankruptcy
就已经临近破产了
since before you returned to Star City.
后来你受伤  这也对股价没有帮助
And your injury, well, it didn't exactly help our stock price.
帕尔默科技的未来就看超能电池了
We staked the future of Palmer Tech on this power cell.
我们需要迈好这一步
We need to put our best foot forward.
现在我估计是迈不出步了
That is not something that I'm exactly able to do right now.
抱歉  我用词不当了
Sorry, poor choice of words.
我的意思是  或许换别人来做展示
What I mean is perhaps it would be better
会更好一些
to let someone else do this presentation.
你说的"别人"
And by "someone else,"
指的是不在轮椅上的人吧
you mean someone not in a wheelchair.
这是为了公司好
This is about doing what's best for the company.
如果不能完美展示
Anything less than a perfect launch
我们就完了
and we are sunk.
对  你说的没错
Right. You're right.
请告知董事会吧
Please let the board know.
我就是想来看看你
Just wanted to check in,
看看你怎么样
see how you were doing.
我觉得这个问题的答案
Well, I think the answer to that question
已经够明显了
is fairly self-evident.
西娅的嗜血性好比一个等式的平衡因子
Thea's bloodlust is the balancing of an equation.
她获得了生命  现在要取走别人的
She was given life and now she needs to take it.
马尔科姆  这我们都知道
Malcolm, we know that already.
但我们不明白的是
What we don't know is--
是你不明白
What you don't know,
而我直到西娅倒下才明白
what I didn't know until Thea collapsed
如果她所获取的生命
is that if the life she owes
不用别人的生命来抵偿
doesn't come from taking others,
就只能用宿主的生命了
it will come from the life of the host.
拜托别把我叫成宿主
Please do not refer to me as the host.
这不是个玩笑
This isn't a joke.
如果你不满足你的嗜血欲望
If you don't indulge this bloodlust,
你就会死的
You will die.
我不明白
I don't understand.
莎拉并不是这样的
Sara wasn't like this.
约翰·康斯坦丁成全了莎拉
John Constantine made Sara whole,
恢复了平衡
and restored the balance.
西娅  我还以为你恢复得不错
Thea, I thought you were doing ok.
那是因为嗜血欲望被暂时钝化了
Because the bloodlust was temporarily blunted.
被什么钝化了
By what?
达米恩·达克
Damien Darhk.
当我们把安迪从蜂巢救出来时
When we rescued Andy from Hive,
我遇到他了
I ran into him.
他想用他的魔力死亡触手杀了我
He tried to kill me with his magic death touch thingie,
但是对我没用
but it didn't work on me.
实际的作用是阻止了嗜血欲
What it did do was stop the bloodlust
暂时的
for a time.
我们得找到达米恩·达克
We need to find Damien Darhk
不论他对她做了什么  要把它永久化
and make whatever he did to her permanent.
奥利弗  就算这有可能
Oliver, even if that were possible,
就算你可以抓到达米恩  让他合作
even if you caught Damien in a more cooperative mood,
他和他的蜂巢早已无影无踪了
he and his Hive have gone to ground.
别告诉我你还没有注意到
Or haven't you noticed?
怎么了
Yeah.
我们那位爱偷东西的朋友
Our sticky-fingered friend
刚在卡德摩斯科技又干了一票
just pulled another job at Cadmus Tech.
卡德摩斯科技
他在你东面  两个街区远  朝南移动
He's two blocks east of you, headed south.
约翰  我现在不行
John, I can't right now.
他这次偷走了一件武器
He stole a weapon this time.
去吧
Just go.
这里一小时也不会发生什么
Nothing's gonna change here in an hour.
我出发了
I'm on my way.
我该朝哪看
Where am I looking?
我们正在搜寻中
We're working on it.
看到他了
Got him!
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
罗伊
Roy?
先是莎拉  然后是雷  接着是约翰的弟弟
First Sara, then Ray, then John's brother.
我们接下来该期待谁的震撼回归呢
Whose shocking return can we look forward to next?
奥利弗  我只是问一下
Oliver, I'm gonna ask this just to ask it.
你确定那是...
Are you sure that it was--
是罗伊  绝对没错
It was Roy. Absolutely.
或者可能是某个人
Or maybe it was just somebody who's able
能使自己看起来像罗伊
to make themselves look like Roy.
别表现得像这有多疯狂似的
Don't act like it's the craziest possibility
我们都经历了这么多
after everything that we've experienced.
真正疯狂的是  罗伊在偷科技公司的东西
What's crazy is Roy stealing from tech companies.
他这次偷了什么
What did he take this time?
一个三极管电容式炸弹
A triode capacitor bomb.
小装备  却能引发巨大的爆炸
Tiny device, really huge boom.
这是艾利克斯今天打的第500通电话了
This is Alex for the 500th time today.
我正准备发短信给你
Hey, I was just texting you.
你怎么...
How did you--
竞选办公室有部秘密电梯
Oh, campaign office has a secret elevator.
什么
What?
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我为了躲避媒体  从侧门进来的
I came in the side to avoid the media.
接到了你的紧急电话  这边情况还好吗
Got your 911. Everything all right?
不太好
No, not really.
莱杰明天要发表这篇东西
Ledger's going to press with it tomorrow,
但我们接到消息
but we got a heads up.
又有人要宣布加入竞选
Someone else is throwing their hat in the ring.
谁
Who?
像是一个政治新手
Political novice it looks like.
我还在整理简介
I'm still working up a bio,
但她好像是突然冒出来的
but she seems to have come out of nowhere
一夜之间在佩尼镇有了竞选办公室
to suddenly have a campaign office in Pennytown.
鲁维·亚当斯
Ruvé Adams.
一个更明智的选择
市长竞选
你认识这人吗
Do you know her from somewhere?
没有  我只是惊讶有了一个竞争对手
No. I'm just surprised to have an opponent.
没错  这可真改变了整个局面
Yeah, it's pretty much a game changer.
抱歉
Sorry.
的确如此
Yes, it is.
我从没怀疑过你的韧性  奎恩先生
I've never doubted you resiliency, Mr. Queen,
但你终究会告诉我的
but you will tell me.
你为什么需要这些地图
Why did you need these maps?
他要是死了  就什么也不能告诉你了
He can't tell you anything if you kill him.
把她弄出去
Get her out of here.
不要
No!
你的纹身代表什么
What did your tattoos reveal, huh?
你是在找什么
What were you trying to find?
你好  奥利弗
Hello, Oliver.
再次见到你真好
It's good to see you again.
你是来支持我的吗
Are you here to endorse me?
鲁维·亚当斯
市长竞选
我想要和你丈夫见面
I want a meeting with your husband.
我看你要是再和我丈夫见一面
I'm not sure you would survive
可不一定能活下来
another meeting with my husband.
这次不打架
No fight this time.
我有个提议要给他
I have a proposition for him.
我在听
I'm listening.
明天十点半  克肖街和第八大街交叉口
Tomorrow, 10:30. Kershaw and 8th.
我们有个新麻烦了
Uh, we have a new problem.
我在查看这两项技术的设计图纸
I was going over the schematics of the two pieces of stolen tech,
想找出罗伊下一步行动的线索
trying to figure out where Roy was going to hit next.
发现什么了吗
Any luck?
没有  我是说  一开始没有
No. I mean, not at first.
电容式炸弹和网络测绘仪
A capacitor bomb and a network mapper,
这就像吊扇和花椰菜之间的关系
that's like a ceiling fan and broccoli.
听起来是个怪异的组合
Sounds like a messy combination.
以这个组合为突破口
Combination being the breakthrough,
我不再尝试去联系
I stopped trying to figure out
这两项技术的共同点了
what the two pieces of tech had in common
转而研究  如果它们以某种方式组合
and started working on what would happen
只连接特定的部件  会发生什么
if they were combined somehow, the components, specifically.
告诉我们些好消息
Tell us something good.
这取决于你对"好"的定义了
Depends on your definition of "good".
但我确定
But I'm pretty sure that
阿美特克的网络测绘仪和卡德摩斯的电容炸弹
Amertek's network mapper and Cadmus' capacitor
理论上可以制成一个网络核弹
could theoretically be used to create a web-nuke.
像个炸弹一样吗
Like a bomb?
罗伊已经偷了一个炸弹了
Roy already stole a bomb.
不是  我说的这个设备
No, I'm talking about a device
可以摧毁整个互联网
that can destroy the entire internet.
这包括银行系统
We're talking banking systems,
核军火库  电力网
nuclear arsenals, power grids.
去年罗伊练"电脑"这个词都不太会写
Last year Roy could barely spell "Computer."
即使我们假设他真的造了这个装置
Even assuming he did build this device--
他为什么还不使用
Why hasn't he used it?
因为它现在还不完整  这种装置
Because it's incomplete. A device like this
需要大量的能源来驱动
needs a really substantial power source to run off of.
猜猜星城哪家公司
And guess what company in Star City
刚刚发明了革命性的下一代电池
just invented a next generation revolutionary battery.
费利西蒂·斯莫克
来电
我并不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
我也不想你伤害我
I don't want you to hurt me, either.
我得把那个东西拿走
Well, I'm going to need to take that.
那看来你得伤害我了
Oh, I think you might have to hurt me, then.
罗伊
Roy.
停下来
Stand down.
他有点不对劲
There's something wrong with him.
我们都看出来了
Yeah, I think that's been established.
罗伊  我们谈谈
Let's talk about this, Roy.
即将就位
Almost in position.
罗伊
Roy.
罗伊  你在做什么
Roy, what are you doing?
仔细听好
Listen very carefully.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定  动手吧
Yes, do it.
等等
No, wait.
你做了什么
What did you do?
小心点把麻醉箭取下来
Take out the tranq, carefully.
希望西斯科装的法拉第笼好用吧
Let's hope the faraday cage Cisco installed in here works.
什么
What?
基本上说是一个防电磁辐射的屏障
Basically a shield for everything broadcast and electromagnetic.
你看到的装置在他哪只眼睛里
Which eye did you see the tech in?
右眼
The right one.
你怎么发现的
How'd you even know he had it?
罗伊的眼睛是蓝色的
Roy's eyes are blue.
我猜它会给放置的人
I'm guessing this was transmitting an av signal,
发射音视频信号
probably to whoever was picking up the tech.
他醒了就可以告诉我们了
Well, he can tell us when he wakes up.
我  我在哪
Wh--where am I?
没事了
It's ok.
我们把隐形眼镜取下来了
We took out the contact.
做的像我们把你杀了
We made it look like we killed you.
你安全了
You're safe.
至少我在这是安全的
While I'm in here, at least.
新据点不错
New lair. Nice.
我听说了你的事
I heard about what happened.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
罗伊  发生了什么
Roy, what happened to you.
我被发现了
I got made.
我在中枢城
I was in Hub city,
有了新名字  新生活  一切重新开始
new name, new life, everything.
直到我收到了一封邮件
And then I got an email.
里面写了什么
Saying what?
叫你去偷一些东西
Steal a bunch of stuff?
不然他就揭露我罗伊·哈珀的身份
Or he'll expose me as Roy Harper.
大家突然发现绿箭没死
Suddenly the Arrow's not dead anymore.
警察就会重新开始调查你
And then the police, they'd be looking at you again.
是谁威胁了你
Who's the blackmailer?
我不知道  从没见过他
I don't know. I've never met him.
但是他自称计算者
But he calls himself the Calculator.
坏人给自己起名就会发生这种囧事
This is what happens when the bad guys name themselves.
罗伊  你应该早点来找我们
Roy, you should have come to us sooner.
-我不能来  -他说的对
- I couldn't. - He's right.
这里面内嵌了摄像机
There's a camera built into this.
这科技真是难以置信
This is really incredible tech.
他可以看到我的每个动作
He could see every single move I made,
和我交谈的每个人
Every person I talked to.
我不能这样暴露了你们
I couldn't just expose you guys like that.
我们会想到办法的
We would have figured something out.
这是我的问题
This is my problem.
但却是因我而起
'cause you were solving my problem.
好了  我们现在的问题是
Ok, well, our problem is that the Calculator
计算者有一切需要的东西来破坏整个网络
now has everything he needs to melt the internet.
我超爱互联网
I love the internet.
也就是说我们必须尽快找到他
Which means we have to find him, fast.
你能反追踪这些部件
Can you backtrace the components,
找到信号源吗
and fgure out where they're broadcast to?
我就是这么想的
Girl, you read my mind.
把夹克脱了  我给你包扎一下
Pop your jacket off, I'll patch you up.
真不敢相信你射了我一箭
Man, I cannot believe you shot me.
说真的
Really?
梅
Mei?
莎朵
Shado.
莎朵已经死了
Shado's dead.
我知道
I know.
你出现幻觉了
You're having a vision.
是你受伤造成的
The result of your injuries.
你不是真实的
You're not real.
的确
No.
但我来告诉你的事是真实的
But what I've come to tell you is.
你要告诉我什么
What have you come to tell me?
你得原谅你自己做过的事
You need to forgive yourself for what you've done.
不幸的是  你得说得具体点
Unfortunately, you're gonna have to be a little more specific.
你本有机会离开这座岛
You had the chance to leave this island,
回到家人身边
to return to your family.
他们非常想念你
They miss you terribly.
我不能回去
I can't go back to my family.
不能像现在这样回去
Not the way that I am now.
那你就该开始改变自己了
Then it's time to start changing.
唯一的出路是通过你自己
The only way out is through Oliver.
阿曼达·沃勒也是这么说的
That's what Amanda Waller said.
通过什么
Through what?
通过你自身的黑暗面
Through your own darkness.
放手吧
Let it go.
我不知道如何放手
I don't know how.
那我来教你
Then I will teach you.
日本  九州
就是这了
This is it.
我并没看到神龛
I see no shrine.
树林就是神龛  泰莱巴
The woods are the shrine, Talibah.
很久以前
In times long past, the people of Japan
日本人在万物中寻找神的踪迹
found their gods in all things.
大自然就是他们的神殿
Nature was their temple.
我必须独自前往
I must do this alone.
如果一个小时之内我没有回来
If I do not return within the hour,
就告诉其他人战争结束了
tell the others the war is over.
[日语] 你迷失方向了吗
[日语]不  我找到了我寻觅的东西
你好  塔苏
Hello, Tatsu.
你看起来不错
You look well.
显然你很适合加入新月会
Being a member of the Crescent Order clearly suits you.
我已经找到了目标
I have found my purpose.
你来日本的目的是什么
What is yours in japan?
我是为了圣莲而来
I've come for the Lotus.
保护圣莲是我的责任
It is my responsibility to keep it safe.
我知道
I know.
真不幸
Unfortunate.
我俩势均力敌
We're evenly matched.
我们必须有人让步  不然没法决出胜负
One of us must yield or this will go on for ages.
我没有别的事情要做
I have nowhere else to be.
我有
I do.
关系到奥利弗·奎恩的事
On a matter that concerns Oliver Queen.
你有两个选择
I see two options.
我们要么打到一人力竭
We keep fighting until one of us drops from exhaustion
要么就放下剑
or we lay down our swords
你听一听我要说的话
and you listen to what I have to say.
也许下次我们能做一些
Maybe next time we can do something
别让我挨刀子或中箭的事
that doesn't involve me getting stabbed or shot at.
只是个想法
Just an idea.
很抱歉把你置于这样的处境
I'm sorry that I put you in this position.
我很肯定是我自己造成的
I'm pretty sure I put myself in this position.
我记得你并不是很高兴
I remember you not being all that happy
我为了保护你的秘密  制造了我死去的假象
that I fakes my death to protect your secret.
我就不该让你这么做
I never should have let you.
你不累吗
Do you ever get tired, you know,
总是像这样  把整个世界的重量
of carrying the weight of the world on your shoulders
都扛在自己肩上
like that all the time?
你的语气很像费利西蒂
You sound like Felicity.
还有狄格尔
And Diggle.
英雄所见略同
Well, great minds.
费利西蒂和约翰说
So what are Felicity and John saying
你现在又肩负了什么责任吗
you're taking responsibility for now?
西娅
Thea.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我出现幻觉了吗
Am I hallucinating?
真的是你
It's really you.
你好吗
How are you?
不是太好
I've been better. Um...
你怎么样
How are you?
你去哪了
Where have you been?
来这做什么
What are you doing here?
你在这里待多...
How-- how long are you--
多久了
here--
西娅
‭Thea?
Thea!
怎么了
What's happening?
我不
I don't...
不知道
I don't know.
天呐
Oh, my God.
拉斯造成的伤口
It's the wound from Ra's.
我打电话报警
I'll call 911.
不  医生也帮不了她
No, doctors can't help her.
保持清醒  西娅  坚强点
Stay with us, Thea. Stay strong.
等一会就好了
Give it a minute, it will pass.
没事了
You're OK.
情况如何
How's it going?
这一小块塑料
This tiny piece of plastic
计算能力比大多数高端笔记本还要强
has more computing power in it than most high-end laptops.
我有点想把它逆向设计  给帕尔默科技用
I have half a mind to reverse engineer it for Palmer Tech.
先说重点
But first?
我在操作系统代码里找到一个微小的缺陷
Yes, I found a tiny flaw in the OS code.
我很肯定我能利用它
I'm pretty sure I can exploit it
打开一个后门  进入他的主机系统
to open a back door to his main computer system.
但这样会令我们暴露吗
Right, but wouldn't that risk exposing us?
你听懂了我的话  让我很骄傲
My pride that you understood what I was saying
可你对我缺乏信心  真是扫兴
is slightly uncut by your lack of faith in me.
我对你绝对有信心  做吧
I've nothing but faith, just do it.
已经做了
I already did.
不管你是谁
Well, well. Whoever you are,
我只想说  我非常佩服
let me just say I am very impressed.
从未有人能破解我的密码
No one's ever been able to break through my encryption before.
好极了
Bravo.
先伪装你的声音
Disguise your voice.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果这话不是出自一个
I would take that as a compliment
想要摧毁网络的疯子之口
if it wasn't coming from some nutjob
我会把它当作是种赞美
who's trying to destroy the internet.
我为什么要摧毁网络
Why would I want to take down the net?
网络不但是我工作的平台
Not only is it where I work,
还有令我疯狂的搞笑猫咪视频
I'm addicted to funny cat videos.
如果你不想摧毁网络
Well, if you're not trying to take down the internet,
那你要网络核弹干什么
what do you need a web-nuke for?
非常聪明  一边跟我说话
Very clever keeping me talking
一边拖延时间攻破我的防火墙
to buy you time to breach my firewall.
你是打算把你的险恶计划告诉我吗
So that's a pass on telling me your evil plan?
这么说吧
Let's put it this way,
如果你想要宣称什么
if you want to make a statement,
你要摧毁的不是一个系统
you don't take down a system,
而是一座城市
you take down a city.
见鬼  他把我踢出来了
Dammit! He shut me out.
不过他已经说出他想干什么了
Not before indicating what his plan might be.
要怎么摧毁一座城...
How do you take down a ci...
糟了
Oh, no.
什么
What?
我一直在想  如果他用网络核弹
I've been thinking about what would happen
来摧毁网络  会造成什么后果
if he used the web-nuke to take down the internet,
但如果他用对了
but if he used it right,
就可以让电网超负荷
overloading the electrical grid,
让医院的设备关闭
shutting down hospital equipment,
造成水管干道破裂
causing water main breaks.
他能害死市里的每一个人
He... he could kill everyone in the city.
所以网络核弹必须要放置在某个地方
So a web-nuke needs to be deployed somewhere.
我们需要知道计算者想要安装的地点
We need to know where the calculator wants to install it.
原则上  我是不会这么叫他的
I am not calling him that on principle,
因为这个代号很烂
'cause it is a lame codename.
好吧  费利西蒂  但我们还是得检查...
OK, Felicity, but we still have to check--
我正在查看网络核弹
I'm conducting a review of all the nodes, sub-nodes,
可能造成最大破坏的所有节点
and network access points where the web-nuke
子节点和网络接入点
would do the most damage.
有发现吗
Any luck?
你为什么总问我这个问题
Why do you always ask me that?
如果有任何发现
If I had any luck looking for what I'm looking for,
我就不会继续找  而是会直接告诉你
I would be telling you about it instead of looking for it.
抱歉  压力太大
Sorry. Stressed.
除了要对付本周的疯子
In addition to our lunatic of the week,
我还要处理帕尔默科技的事
I have Palmer Tech to look after.
帕尔默科技
Palmer Tech.
去年雷在研究一个叫攻城锤的程序
Ray worked up something last year called a Battering Ram,
大致就是能攻破网络安全的东西
basically something that could crash through cyber security.
不是商业应用程序  但是
No commercial application, but--
你能用它再次进入计算者的系统吗
Can you use it to get back into the Calculator's system?
别再这样叫他了  我说真的
Stop calling him that, I'm serious.
你的黑暗面就是内疚
Your darkness is guilt.
你取了很多人的性命
You've taken many lives.
最近是你心上人的哥哥
The life of your love's brother most recently.
我没爱上泰安娜
I'm not in love with Taiana.
她帮你拿回了亚马逊号上的地图
She helped you recover the maps from the Amazo.
她照顾你直至康复
She nursed you back to health.
而你回报她的全是谎言
And all she's received from you in return is a lie.
睁开双眼
Open your eyes.
这是什么
What's this?
柯蒂斯·霍特  你看到攻城槌了吗
Curtis Holt, have you seen the Battering Ram?
就是雷去年发明的那个很厉害的技术
It's this kick ass piece of tech that Ray invented last year.
圆柱形  钛合金外壳
Um, cyndrical shape, titanium shell.
我在准备一场暴力攻击
I'm gearing up for a brute force attack.
小心那个
Look out for that...
我需要集合所有的火力
And I need all the firepower I can muster.
高脚凳  没事了
...stool. Uh, never mind.
一天之内  轮椅就用得
Hey, you've gotten pretty slick on that thing
这么顺手  怎么回事
in the last 24 hours. What happened?
找到了
Yes! I got it.
谢谢你  柯蒂斯  你最好了
Thanks, Curtis. You're the best.
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
是你在这里来去如风
You're the one who's whipping around here
干劲十足
like a house on fire.
整座城市陷入危机时  我就会这样
Well, that is what happens when the entire city is at stake.
但现在只是整个公司而已
But now when it's just, say, an entire company.
丹尼斯先生说你不打算
Mr. Dennis says you're no longer
向董事会展示超级电池了
presenting the power cell to the board.
我的预演就是一场空前灾难
Well, my dry run was an epic disaster.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
那...那确实是一次很惨 的失败
It was...It was a spectacular failure.
确实是很糟糕
Like, it was really bad.
但如果这位费莉西蒂参与结果就会不一样
But it wouldn't have been if this Felicity had come in.
这位坐着轮椅
You know, the one who wheels in here
像刚才那样风风火火的人
kicking ass and taking names like you just did.
这是不一样的
This is different.
对  不一样
No, it's not.
你身上有两个费莉西蒂  费莉西蒂
There's two Felicitys, Felicity.
一个在会议室里
The one in that boardroom
因为坐着轮椅便开始怀疑自己
whose wheelchair makes her doubt herself.
而这个费莉西蒂
And this Felicity,
闪耀着活力之光
a brilliant force of nature.
这个公司需要的是第二个费莉西蒂
This company needs the second Felicity.
劳蕾尔跟我说了
Laurel told me.
你还好吗
You ok?
我感觉好点了
I'm feeling a bit better.
我有些事要处理
Hey. I'm working on something.
如果我要杀的是个恋童癖
If it's a pedophile for me to kill,
马尔科姆肯定已经在暴打那个人了
Malcolm's already been pitching that one hard.
你不是一个杀手  西娅
You're not a killer, Thea.
那不该是你的生活方式
That's not a way for you to live.
达米恩·达克却可能是杀手
But it sounds like Damien Darhk might be.
我肯定他现在正恨不得帮我们呢
Yeah, I'm sure he's just itching to do us a favor.
我们会知道的
We're gonna find out.
我安排了一次会面
I arranged a meeting.
他又不会真的想帮我
It's not like he's gonna be willing to help me.
也许我们有他想要的东西
Maybe there's something that he wants,
我可以跟他交易
something I can trade him.
奥利  这不仅疯狂
Ollie, that's insane.
简直愚蠢  我...
Not to mention stupid. I...
我不能让你欠达克人情
I can't let you owe Darhk a favor.
我也不能让你死
And I can't let you die.
我不会让你死的
I won't.
那不是你能决定的
That's not up to you.
我知道所有事你都想一个人扛
Look, I know how you take everything on,
所有人的问题
everyone's problems.
这也是我最爱你的一点
It's one of the things I love the most about you.
但这次你无法解决  奥利
But you can't fix this one, Ollie.
我一定要试试
I have to try.
不  你不必
No, you don't.
这是我的选择
It's my choice.
这是我的人生
It's my life.
她很倔强  不是吗
She's stubborn, isn't she?
一定是她从你这边继承下来的性格
Definitely something she gets from your side of the family.
这都没关系了
It doesn't matter.
因为你准备穿上战衣
Because you're going to go hood in head
去找达米恩·达克
to Damien Darhk.
我是恶魔首领  我有消息来源
I am the demon's head. I have my resources.
而且我还知道怎么隔着门偷听
And I know how to put my ear up against a door.
放弃你无比愚蠢的计划吧
Leaving the epic stupidity of your plan aside,
西娅说得对
Thea's right.
这不该由我们决定
This is neither of our decisions.
马尔科姆  难道你想她死吗
Malcolm, do you want her to die?
当然不是
Of course not.
你知道我有多想
Do you have any idea how badly
给她一把刀
I want to put a knife in her hand
逼她给某人喉咙一刀吗
and force her to slit someone's throat?
我差一点就把人拉来任她宰割
I've come this close to dragging someone in here for her to kill.
我没有这么做是因为这一直是我想要的
And the reason I don't is because that would be about my feelings
而不是西娅想要的
and not Thea's.
奥利弗  有时候大爱无言
Oliver, sometimes the greatest act of love is no action at all.
这是她的人生  她的选择
It's her life. It's her choice.
用雷的技术去打击这家伙
This almost feels like cheating,
感觉就像在作弊
using Ray's tech to beat this guy.
找到了
Got it.
他正在弗林特山数据库中安装网络核弹
He's installing the web-nuke at Flint Hill Data Farm.
安装
Installing?
是的  他现在就在安装
Yeah, he's doing it right now.
通知奥利弗
Get Oliver.
计算者在弗林特山-911
设备准备完毕
Device is onsite.
好极了
Dandy.
//检测到蠕虫病毒
稍等一下
Hang on a second.
想我了吗
Miss me?
蠕虫病毒安装中
我太想念这一切了
I have seriously missed this.
守望者  我们已就位
Overwatch, we're on station.
我正在寻找网络核弹
I'm trying to find the web-nuke,
但是对方察觉到我黑进了他的系统
but our adversary knows I'm in his system
他正在想办法赶我出去
and he's trying to kick me out.
不过我看到了他的路由协议
I did get a look at his protocols, though.
如果这个网络核弹上线
And if the web-nuke goes online,
八千人将死在他手上
he could kill 8,000 people.
我觉得那只是保守估计
I'd say that's a conservative estimate.
仅炸掉煤气管道就能干掉三千人
Blowing the gas mains alone would kill 3,000.
等着看我为地铁精心编写了什么吧
Just wait till you see what I've got planned for the subway cars.
听起来不错  到监狱里给我写信细讲吧
Good story. Write me a letter. From prison.
攻城槌确实是个妙招
The battering ram was a neat trick,
但是你们阻止我的唯一方法
but the only way you're going to stop me
就是在现场移除网络核弹
is by removing the web-nuke on site.
[状态]     运行中  91%
我想你通常只是
And I suspect that you don't come out
幕后操纵吧
from behind that keyboard much.
那是因为我有朋友
That's what I have friends for.
有谁知道该怎么断开这玩意吗
Ok, so does anyone know how to disconnect this thing?
我也带了朋友
I brought friends, too.
找了雇佣兵
Hired mercenaries.
在暗网里招募的人总给人惊喜
It's amazing who you can find on the dark web.
你总是要华丽登场  是不是
Always got to make an entrance, don't you?
不好意思  有场见面我决定不去了
Sorry, there was a meeting that I decided not to go to.
我知道我也算有点经验了
Look, I know it's been a while for me,
但这声音可不是什么好兆头  对吧
but this still isn't a good thing, right?
我差点就不忍心击败你了
You know, I almost feel bad about beating you.
我很少遇到像你那么聪明的人
Rarely do I get to meet someone with your talents.
设防  执行
你干了什么
What did you do?
我想专业点说就是你被我黑了
Boom! I believe the technical term is I powned you.
即便如此  我也能攻破你的防火墙
Be that as it may, I can breach your firewall
比攻破披头士歌曲的数字版权还快
faster than I can remove the DRMs off a Beatles tune.
各位  网络核弹已经连接好了
Guys, the web-nuke is hard wired in.
虽说我也不指望你们能有多了解
Not to get too inside baseball on you,
但我要你们炸掉这玩意
but I need you to blow the thing up.
我们有多少时间
How much time do we have?
说来话长
It's a long story,
但介于”我想与你牵手"
but somewhere between "I Want to Hold Your Hand"
和"嘿朱迪”之间
and "Hey, Jude."
正在启动炸弹
Priming the explosive.
有点不对劲
Something's not working.
他在干扰爆震频率
He's jamming the detonation frequencies.
好  按老方法来
Ok, do this the old-fashioned way
手动启动电源吧
and manually set the charge.
那我们怎么在启动瞬间
Yeah, but how do we do that
来得及离开这里呢
and get out of here in one piece?
一定要有人垫后
Someone has to stay behind.
我来吧
I'll do it.
就算从远处用箭引爆C4[一种塑胶爆炸物]
Even if you triggered the C4 with an arrow at a distance,
你也得赶快逃出爆炸范围
you still need to outrun the blast radius.
我能做到
I can do that.
就算穿得一身红你也不是闪电侠  罗伊
Just because you're wearing red doesn't make you the Flash, Roy.
我没说这没有风险
I didn't say it wasn't gonna be risky.
你刚刚开始了新生活
You just got a fresh start.
我不想让你失去这一切
I don't want you to throw it all away.
是我把找这个疯子带进了你们的生活
I'm the one who brought this maniac in your lives.
我必须得这么干  这是我的选择
I need to do this. This is my choice.
是我的人生
It's my life.
好吧
Ok.
外面等你  小子
See you outside, kid.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你一定要拼命跑
Hey, you run like hell.
我会的
Yeah.
你们最好离开这里
You guys might want to get out of here.
快啊  罗伊
Come on, Roy.
快点
Come on!
//检测到蠕虫病毒
设防  执行
感觉像骑自行车
Just like riding a bicycle
很高兴你能回来  罗伊
It's good to have you back, Roy.
我们很想你
You've been missed.
好吧  不要习惯有我在
Well, don't get too used to me.
我又要继续隐姓埋名了
I'm gonna have to go underground again.
计算者知道了我的身份  我得藏更深
Even deeppr now that the calculator knows who I am.
他为什么没能在网上散布消息
What's to keep him from posting it on the Internet?
我好像在他的系统里植入了病毒
I might have installed a virus in his system
把他全部有关罗伊的消息抹去了
that wiped out everything he had on Roy.
抱歉我得走了
I'm sorry I can't stay.
不光是对你们  也对西娅
Not just for you guys, but for Thea.
她会理解的
She'll understand.
她会好起来的  奥利弗
She's gonna be ok, Oliver.
不论她做出了什么决定
Well, whatever she decides,
我都会支持她
I'm gonna back her play.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
我还以为你的烧退不下去了
I thought the fever would never break.
我去给你弄点水喝
I'll get you some water.
泰安娜
Taiana.
我得告诉你一些事
I need to tell you something.
别着急
It's ok.
不管你要说什么  先喝点水吧
Whatever it is, it can wait until you've had some water.
我对你撒谎了
I lied to you.
我告诉过你是康克林杀了你的哥哥
When I said that Conklin killed your brother,
其实不是这样
that was a lie.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't understand.
长久以来我一直试图逃避
I have this darkness inside of me
我内心的黑暗面
that I've been trying to escape for the longest time.
现在我找到了解决办法
And I think that I found a way,
但首先我得祈求你的原谅
but first I need to earn your forgiveness.
原谅你什么
For what?
我并不知道瓦勒徳是你的哥哥
I didn't know that Vlad was your brother.
虽然事出有因  但都不重要了
There are reasons, but they don't matter,
也无法改变我做过的事
they don't change what I did.
是我杀了你哥哥
I killed your brother.
不
No.
真不敢相信我竟然被你说服了
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
你不会有问题的  祝好运
You are gonna be great. Break a leg.
抱歉
Sorry.
没关系
Ok.
欢迎大家
Welcome.
这一天我已期盼多日
This is a day I have looked forward to for a very long time.
帕尔默科技
因为今天我站在
Because today I stand
许多巨人的肩膀上
on the shoulders of many giants.
尼古拉·特斯拉  托马斯·爱迪生
Nikola Tesla, Thomas Edison,
雷·帕尔默  当然还有柯蒂斯·霍特
Ray Palmer, and of course, Curtis Holt
他们一直致力于
Their work has always
让世界变得更美好
been about making this world a better place.
而今天
And today,
我们朝着那目标又迈出了一步
we get to take another step towards that goal.
众所周知  电池技术数十年来实际上
As you know, battery technology has been at a virtual standstill
一直在瓶颈期  电池耐用性和充电速度
for decades, with batteries lasting, nor charging any faster
并不比七十年代有何进步
than they did in the 1970s.
直到现在
Until now.
今天帕尔默科技很荣幸地介绍
Today Palmer Tech is pleased to introduce
这款超级电池  100%可循环利用
the power cell, a 100% recyclable battery.
它可供电动车跑上数千里
It can charge an electric car for thousands of miles.
就在此刻  单凭这一小块电池
And right now, it is single-handedly
不仅可以为整场演说提供电量
not only powering this entire presentation,
也可以为整栋大楼供电
but this entire building.
她说得太棒了  对吧
She is something else, isn't she?
绝对是
You have no idea.
重新开始的话你应该去当个护士
You know, you should be a nurse in your new life.
你天生就是这块料
You're a natural at it.
但唯一的问题是  我只会照顾一个人
The only problem is, I am a one-patient man,
而且我早就向你承诺过了
and I'm already committed to you.
这就是你要离开的原因吗
Is that why you're leaving?
听着  我知道  星城到处都是
Look, I get it, Star City is filled with too many people
能认出你的人
who can recognize you.
你知道的  我想过无论如何都要留下
You know, I thought about staying anyway.
为了你
For you.
你知道你能为我做些什么吗
You know what you could do for me?
去过你精彩丰富的生活
Go live an amazing life.
结婚生子
Get married, have a couple of kids.
再买一辆小货车
Get a minivan.
过正常人的生活
Just go be normal.
在这世上  只有你幸福了
There's nothing in this world
我才能更加宽慰
that would make me happier than that.
你知道的  如果一切可以重来
You know, if I could do all of this over again,
我愿每一件事都有你陪伴
I would do every single one of those things with you.
我也是
Me, too.
我爱你  西娅·奎恩
I love you, Thea Queen.
我也爱你  罗伊·哈珀
I love you, Roy Harper.
你在台上的表现太棒了
You were amazing out there.
谢谢
Thanks.
西娅现在怎么样了
How's Thea doing?
我准备去看看她
I'm gonna go check on her now.
我要去跟柯蒂斯做汇报了
I'm just gonna debrief with Curtis,
发信息告诉我她的情况  好吗
but text me how she's doing. Ok.
好的
OK.
天呐
Oh, my god.
爸爸
Dad?
她还好吗
How is she?
在休息呢
‭Resting.
你那新对头达米恩在哪里
Where's your new BFF Damien?
不知道
I don't know.
就像你说的  这是西娅的决定
Like you said, this is Thea's decision,
不是我的
it's not mine.
奥利弗  我知道这感觉不好
Oliver, I know it feels wrong,
但是你做的是对的
but you did the right thing.
不管感觉如何  没有你我都做不到
However it feels, I couldn't have done it without you.
马尔科姆  谢谢
Malcolm, thank you.
你所做的一切
For everything.
奥利弗  西娅不好了
Oliver, it's Thea.
星城医院
急诊入院处
她还会昏迷多久
How long will she be in a coma?
现在她勉强处在三级格拉斯哥昏迷状态
Right now she's barely a 3 on the Glasgow Scale.
预后情况不太乐观
Prognosis isn't good.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
西娅求你坚持住
Thea please don't go.
只有一个办法能保住她
There's only one way to prevent that.
我父亲曾告诉我有种叫圣莲的长生之药
My father once told me of an elixir known as Lotus.
能够压制复活泉水的副作用
Capable of countering the effects of the Lazarus Pit.
联盟的敌人研发的秘密武器
A secret weapon developed by the League's enemies.
你有吗
Do you have it?
有
I do.
只要答应我一个条件我就免费给你
And I will freely give it to you on one condition.
我要你杀了马尔科姆·梅林
I want you to kill Malcolm Merlyn.